Hello

I'm Sara Hamme

Denver, CO 80223 (989) 415-7509 sarahamme7@gmail.com github.com/sarahamme

Objective

Looking to join a team as an UX Engineer by implementing user interaction following client-approved mock-ups, such as wireframes, visual design comprehensive layouts, and prototypes. Bringing a keen eye for details, strong ability to implement mock-ups, and understanding of great user experience design; one year of experience in visual UI /UX/ front-end development work, JavaScript, CSS, and jQuery, XHTML 1.1, and Web Standard HTML5.

Experience

May 2018- Present

Software Programmer at University of Denver, Denver, CO - Full-Stack Programmer

- Created the app Hike It Up! taking REI, MapQuest, and The Weather Channels API's to help users find hiking trails in their city
- Lead the UX development process in Hike It Up!
- Work with front-end languages and frameworks such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, and React.
- Work with back-end languages and frameworks such as Node.Js, MySql, MongoDb, and Express

July 2018- Present

Mountain Toad Brewery, Golden, CO - Bartender

- Fostered good customer relations to promote company goodwill
- Worked registers daily to authorize returns and exchanges, and audit receipts
- Pour and educate customers on the craft beer selections

September 2017 - July 2018

Boxcar Coffee Roasters, Denver, CO - Barista

- Make and obtain to recipe standards in specialty coffee
- Speak and interact with customers
- Worked registers daily to authorize returns and exchanges, and audit receipts.

September 2016 - September 2017

Downtown Market Grand Rapids, Grand Rapids, MI – *Administrative Assistant/Digital Marketing Intern*

- Host and assistant of event planning, project management, program coordination, and community building activities.
- Assist with promotions, marketing/advertising plans and campaigns; specifically Instagram

Education

May 2018 - October 2018

University of Denver, Denver, CO - Software Programing

6 month bootcamp learning: computer Science applied to Javascript, browser based technologies, PHP, databases, Node.JS, quality assurance, and internet marketing.

Ongoing

Udemy, Denver, CO - Software Programing

Full-Stack Web Developer Bootcamp, The Complete Javascript Course, and Node with React Full-Stack Web Development

August 2012 - December 2016

Grand Valley State University, Grand Rapids, MI - Hospitality Management

Obtained a Bachelor's degree while participating in NCAA division II swimming and diving.

Continued Education

Code Academy - HTML, CSS, Javascript Javascript30 - 30 days of Javascript with Wes Bos